{
    "subject": "Gertrude_of_Hohenburg",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Rudolph_I_of_Germany",
    "human_readable": "Gertrude of Hohenburg is married to Rudolph I of Germany.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9646121859550476,
            "question": "Is Gertrude of Hohenburg related to Rudolph I of Germany?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9439533948898315,
            "question": "To whom is Gertrude of Hohenburg married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9323591589927673,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Gertrude of Hohenburg and Rudolph I of Germany?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.902280867099762,
            "question": "Who is married to Rudolph I of Germany?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8896985054016113,
            "question": "Is Rudolph I of Germany married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8833370804786682,
            "question": "Name the wife of Rudolph I of Germany."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.837492823600769,
            "question": "Who was the spouse of Rudolph I of Germany?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7919147610664368,
            "question": "Who is Gertrude of Hohenburg?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7193661332130432,
            "question": "What is the name of Rudolph I of Germany's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6896982192993164,
            "question": "What is Gertrude of Hohenburg's marital status?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Gertrude of Hohenburg is married to Rudolph I of Germany.",
            "html": "yago_25897_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Rudolph I of Germany's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_25897_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Gertrude of Hohenburg?",
            "html": "yago_25897_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who was the spouse of Rudolph I of Germany?",
            "html": "yago_25897_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25897_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25897_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25897_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25897_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25897_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25897_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25897_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25897_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25897_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25897_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents support the triple, as there are multiple mentions of Gertrude of Hohenburg being married to Rudolph I of Germany (Rudolf I of Germany), including in files `1.txt`, `25.txt`, and others."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provided contain information about the marriage between Rudolph I of Germany and Gertrude of Hohenberg. For instance, in the document located at `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_25897/re-ranker-msmarco/29.txt`, it states: \"In 1245 [her future husband] Rudolph I King Romans (age 26) and Gertrude Hohenburg (age 20) were married.\" This supports the triple that Gertrude of Hohenburg is married to Rudolph I of Germany."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}